Jean Araujo

Multimedia designer with sense of humor

South Thomaston, ME - Email me on Indeed: indeed.com/r/Jean-Araujo/ca8a70070ea19afd

I have 12 years of experience in web design and art direction for online education, including extended experience in an academic environment, and in the financial market, using the latest multimedia technologies to design user interfaces and interaction for courses, and interacting with students and professors to achieve the best practices.

I assure visual integrity with my areas of expertise including typography, logo design, print media, photography and photo retouch, audio (sound design), video edition, illustration and social media, throughout all the communication media.

I'm constantly learning and improving. I have a natural eye for detail and focus on usability to create attractive and functional design. Everything surrounding me is a source of inspiration for my work.

I'm currently living in Maine but willing to relocate or work remotely.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Web Designer

Treina E-Learning - São Paulo, SP - 2008 to 2012

Financial market training

64 Dr. Fernandes Coelho Street São Paulo, SP, Brazil

www.treina.com.br

Web Designer

Cruzeiro do Sul University - São Paulo, SP - 2001 to 2008

High School, College and University

255 Dr Ussiel Cirilo, Avenue São Paulo, SP, Brazil

www.unicsul.br

EDUCATION

Associate in Art Education

Cruzeiro do Sul University - São Paulo, SP 2007 to 2010

Post-grad in Web Sites Engineering

Cruzeiro do Sul University - São Paulo, SP 2003 to 2005

Associate in Information Systems

Cruziero do Sul University - São Paulo, SP 2001 to 2003

SKILLS

Site layout, Icon design, Photography and Image retouch, Logo design, Branding, Typography, Online education course developer, Interaction design, Instructional design, Blackboard and WebCT LMS administration, Illustration, Sound design, Music composition and production

LINKS

http://www.behance.net/sinthie